maingames.co.id 2018-08-29

# MainGames | Play the Best Games of 2018 !

**Maingames company (www.maingames.com)** respects the privacy rights of our users and is committed to protecting the information collected through its products, services, and websites accessed through any internet-capable hardware platform including personal computers, mobile computers, smartphones, or in-game applications or any software platform including Online Services.  
Maingames recognizes the importance of protecting information collected from users and has adopted this privacy policy to inform users about how Maingames gathers, stores, and uses information derived from their use of Maingames products, services and online sites.

This policy is current as of its last revision date. However, please note that this policy may be amended from time to time to reflect changes and additions to the privacy policy. Please check back for the most current version before relying on any of the provisions in this privacy policy. Should you have any questions relating to Privacy Policy, please contact us at [cs@maingames.com](mailto:cs@maingames.com).

  1. **What information does Maingames collect?**
    1. Personal/Non-personal Data  
We may collect and process the following data about you: 
      * information that you provide us with when you fill in forms when accessing and/or using our Services, or when you create an account with us;
      * details of your use of our Services and the resources that you access (for example, information about how and when you play our Games or visit our Website, what device you use to access our Services.
      * if you contact us or respond to messages and communications that we send to you, we may keep a record of that correspondence; 
      * your interactions with us on our social media channels such as Facebook and Google Plus (G+);
      * we may obtain information about you from third parties who hold data about you and who agree to share this data with us; and
      * information we collect via cookies and other similar technologies, as explained further below.
    2. Cookies & Advertising  
We use cookies and other similar technologies in our Services. These technologies operate either by (i) placing a small file which stores some information on your computer or mobile device; and/or (ii) by accessing information on your device. We use cookies and similar technologies: 
      * to allow us to recognize you and your device, for example by identifying your IP address;
      * to allow our Services to interact with a third party social network or platform (where you have chosen to allow such interaction);
      * to allow our payment processors to process your payment instructions;
      * to enable us and third parties to provide you with more customized services, for example to provide our services in the correct language or to enable the provision of more relevant advertising to you; and
      * to collect data such as: your device’s model, operating system and screen size, the other applications installed on your device, and information about how you use our Services.

By accessing and/or using our Services you consent to our use of cookies and similar technologies in accordance with this Privacy Policy. You can disable cookies through your web or phone browser settings but you may find you are not able to enjoy all the features of our Services if you do so. Alternatively, if you do not wish us to collect data as described in this section, you should stop using our Services.

Advertisers on mobile devices sometimes use advertising (or ad) identifiers to enable and optimize their advertising. Ad identifiers are non-permanent, non-personal, device identifiers such as the Android advertising ID and/or Apple’s ID for advertising, or IDFA. When we advertise our Services on mobile devices, we may use your device’s advertising identifier and other information associated with it, to help us to deliver ads that relate to your interests and to improve and measure the effectiveness of ad campaigns. You can choose to prevent your device’s ad identifier being used for interest based advertising, or you can reset your device’s ad identifier, by changing the settings of your device. Settings vary from device to device but if you are using an Apple device with iOS 7 or later you can find the ad identifier settings under Settings>Privacy>Advertising, and if you are using a Google Android device running Android 2.3 or later you can find the ad identifier settings in your app drawer under Google Settings>Ads.

    3. Payment Information  
When you purchase Services on our website(s), we may collect certain payment information from you on behalf of our payment service providers, but this information is temporarily cached in a way that is unreadable by Maingames. When you purchase items via our apps (such as those you can purchase in the Apple App Store or Google Play Store) we do not collect or store any payment information from you.
  2. **How will we use your Personal Information?**  
You agree that we (or a supplier or group company acting on our behalf and only under our instructions) may use your Personal Information for the purposes of: 
    1. contacting you, for example as part of our customer support or to send you updates about our Services;
    2. managing your account and relationship with us and improving your experience when you use our Services;
    3. improving our Services, for example by helping us fix bugs or by providing Services updates;
    4. research, surveying, and engaging with you, for example by sending you communications (including by email) for these purposes;
    5. marketing and promotion of our Services or related products, for example sending you communications (including by email) for these purposes on our, or a third party's behalf. For example, we might send you information about new games or events. If you do not want us to use your data in this way, please let us know by contacting us at [cs@maingames.com;](mailto:cs@maingames.com;)
    6. to personalize and optimize our Services, promotional content and advertising to you. For example, we may use the information we collect through cookies, ad identifiers and similar technologies to show you ads you may be interested in. If you do not want us to use your data in this way, you can opt-out by following the steps at section 3 above;
    7. to create reports, analysis or similar services for use by us for the purposes of research or business intelligence, for example to track potential problems or trends with our Services;
    8. preventing cheating, crime or fraud. We may also need to pass your information to fraud prevention agencies and other organizations involved in crime and fraud prevention;
    9. as otherwise expressly set out in this Privacy Policy or as required by law.
  3. **Will we share your Personal Information with third parties?**  
We will only share your data with third parties (for example, our group companies or suppliers): 
    1. with your consent (including as set out in this Privacy Policy);
    2. as reasonably necessary in order to provide the Services to you (for example, by providing your Personal Information to suppliers we may use to fulfil the Services or to communicate with you);
    3. where it is necessary to carry out your instructions (for example, to process a payment instruction we must provide your Personal Information to our payment processors);
    4. where your data is on an anonymous and aggregated basis, meaning you could not be personally identified from it;
    5. when you submit information as part of a competition or otherwise interact with our social media channels (for example, by providing a testimonial about one of our Services) we may publish the information you submitted, alongside your name and home country on our website(s) and social media channels;
    6. as we reasonably believe is permitted by law or regulation;
    7. in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms and conditions and/or any other agreement with you; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Maingames, our users, or others;
    8. in the event that there is a sale of the assets of Maingames or corporate restructuring, or as a result of a change of control of Maingames or one of its group companies, or in preparation of any of these events. Any third party to which Maingames transfers of sells Maingames's assets will have the right to continue to use the personal and other information that you provide to us in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy. We will not sell or rent your information to any third party outside of these circumstances.
  4. **Maingames Profile**  
Users of our Services may be automatically assigned a profile which is visible to other users of our Services. Your profile may include your username, photos, or other game play information and details of which other Maingames account holders have viewed your profile. Your profile will be visible to other users of our Services.
  5. **For how long will we retain your information?**  
We will retain your Personal Information for as long as is necessary to fulfil the purposes for which it was collected or as needed to provide you with Services. We may retain your Personal Information after you have closed any account you have with us or after we have stopped providing Services to you if retention of your Personal Information is reasonably necessary to comply with our legal obligations, meet regulatory requirements, resolve disputes between members, prevent fraud, cheating or abuse, or enforce this Privacy Policy or any other agreement we may have with a user.
  6. **How do we protect your Personal Information?**  
The security of your Personal Information is very important to us. We maintain appropriate technical and physical safeguards to protect your Personal Information against accidental or unlawful destruction or loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access, use and all other unlawful forms of processing of the data in our possession. However, since the internet is not a completely secure environment we cannot guarantee that information you transmit via our Games will not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of any of our safeguards.
  7. **Your rights in relation to your Personal Information**  
We want to make sure that your Personal Information is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to modify, correct or remove information by contacting us at the email address above. Information that you have shared via our Services on any social network or third party platform cannot be amended or deleted by us where it is in the control of that social network or third party platform. In addition, where any third party copies information which you have made available via the use of our Services (for example, one of your friends on a social network you allow to interact with your account), we may not be able to amend or delete it because it may not be in our control.  
You have the right to ask us not to use your Personal Information for marketing purposes. To change your marketing preferences, or to unsubscribe, please contact us at [cs@maingames.com](mailto:cs@maingames.com).
  8. **How to contact us?**  
To find out more about how your Personal Information will be used, please contact us at [cs@maingames.com](mailto:cs@maingames.com).
  9. **Complaints**  
We hope that you won't have any complaints about us or our Services. If you are unhappy with our use of your Personal Information then please contact our customer services department by emailing to [cs@maingames.com](mailto:cs@maingames.com)  
You also have the right to complain to your local data protection authority if there is a problem.
  10. **Legal Matters**  
If any court or other competent authority finds any of the terms of this Privacy Policy to be invalid or unenforceable, the other terms of this Privacy Policy will not be affected.  
This Privacy Policy is governed by and interpreted in accordance with the laws of Singapore. Any dispute arising in connection with this Privacy Policy will be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of Singapore unless you choose the courts of your home country. We are constantly innovating and looking for new ways to improve our Services and our Games. We may therefore amend this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect such improvements or any other changes to our business. We will try to tell you about any significant changes to this Privacy Policy which we feel may disadvantage you in any material way. If you object to any of the changes you should immediately stop using our Services and close any account you may have with us.
